<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Dzmitry Kishylau</title><link>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Dzmitry Kishylau</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 11:45:35 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Argentina Bike Trip</title><link>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/argentina-bike-trip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 11:45:35 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/argentina-bike-trip/</guid><description>&lt;p>I went on a bikepacking trip in Argentina for two weeks. The route started in Salta, went for more than 500 miles along &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/National_Route_40_(Argentina)">Routa 40&lt;/a> and ended in Talampaya National Park. I then spent a couple of days exploring Buenos Aires.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Exploratory Data Analysis vs Data Visualization</title><link>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/eda-vs-datavis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 20:57:44 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/eda-vs-datavis/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to uplevel my data visualization skills for a while, and I finally found time to do it. The process is going very slow, partly because it&amp;rsquo;s a little unclear what &amp;ldquo;uplevel&amp;rdquo; means in this specific case, and when I&amp;rsquo;m going to be &amp;ldquo;done&amp;rdquo;.
So far I&amp;rsquo;ve read two classic (or just old, if you like) books - John Tukey&amp;rsquo;s Exploratory Data Analysis and William Cleveland&amp;rsquo;s Visualizing Data. I then picked two random datasets on Kaggle and tried to apply what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned.</description></item><item><title>Mining data in Web3 Twitter</title><link>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/web3-twitter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 09:21:59 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/web3-twitter/</guid><description>I spent several weeks in November-December building a data pipeline and a website to surface urls that trend on web3/crypto Twitter. This was a collaboration project with Nadia and Jared from South Park Commons. They were interested in making web3 development easier while I was interested in getting some non-trivial dataset to practice my data wrangling skills. In the end I learned a lot more about Google Cloud than about time series analysis or data visualization, but that was fun anyway.</description></item><item><title>Tokenomics of Bliss</title><link>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/tokenomics-of-bliss/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 22:05:25 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/tokenomics-of-bliss/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a bit of time looking at various projects in crypto space and trying to make sense of them. This post tries to cover a vast part of space that is sometimes referred to as &amp;ldquo;tokenomics&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Choosing Blog Platform</title><link>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/choosing-blog-platform/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 15:09:54 -1000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/choosing-blog-platform/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ok, I know this blog so far is only about blogging, which is never a good sign, but I spent about a week looking at various platforms and frameworks, so there has to be something useful in all of that.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What Is This Blog</title><link>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/what-is-this-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 20:47:59 -1000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.dkishylau.com/posts/what-is-this-blog/</guid><description>&lt;p>I plan to use this blog as a random collection of reports about my side projects and things that I learned or looked into along the way.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>